{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"cvjeta","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aroban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"as","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asopis","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"empres","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešalj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeset","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokratnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokut","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"inele","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itanka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"izma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uditi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"udo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrst","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"druk","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dvoto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ivan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kle","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"klju","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kornja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kota","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kov","osnova2":"eg","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"krma","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lopo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljulja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"masla","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mladun","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mom","osnova2":"ad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naslonja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"natika","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"natje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"novorođen","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"njema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uh","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ogrta","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pješ","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"je","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pokaziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pokriva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"presko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"raj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"savija","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"strunja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tratin","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"ionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"usisava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"uspinja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zajedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zavi","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ži","osnova2":"ara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"Boži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"boži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"up","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"došaš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"goš","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"izi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"kozli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k%ur%uš","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"eha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"uhica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"miši","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"nesre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pam","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"plu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"polno","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pove","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ražnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"si","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"snjegovi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"spava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"srnda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"staja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"stolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"svu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"štapi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"trudno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"uš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vrti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"zada","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
